[{"answer": "Great", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I think so", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I can't tell anymore", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Feel? What's that", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Cleanin", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Nobody does. You know, nobody knows what to do. You just close your eyes and you hope for the best. I really think they're happy if you just make an effort", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You got the tap", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Nobody's faking", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I faked it", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Fake, fake, fake, fake", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Uuuhm, all the time", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'm stunned, I'm shocked! How many times did you do this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "All the time?", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No. None", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Faked 'em all", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "How did she do it? She's like Meryl Streep this woman. And I had to work the equipment. I'm not unskilled, I'm in the union. If she'd at least told me, maybe I could have done something about it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What could you have done", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "All right, see you later", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "All right, see you later", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Bye. ", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It's terrible", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yeah, of course I got it at my friend's", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "So what do you want me to do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Restitution? You want restitution? Why should I give you restitution", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "When you put that fruit out, that's where it ends for me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I stand behind my fruit", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You know this whole place is going vrrrrrrrrrrrrt, downhill. I could have come in here last week with a bad plum but I let it go", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh now you don't want my business", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well let me put a solution for yo", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No, I don't want your business and from this moment you're banned from the store, you're banned", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Generally", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No, I feel full after the Risotto", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What, no, it doesn't matter. my friend, I don't care", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Goodnight. Thanks for a really fabulous evening ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yes I'm upset, can't you tell", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No I can't, maybe you're faking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I'm sorry too", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well stop being such a baby", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You're a baby!", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What, what are you talking about", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I'll tell you something els", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "That's exactly what I'm saying", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "That's exactly what I'm saying", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "You're banned.", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I'm waiting", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yeah I got your fins. You got my poker chips", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "All right. You got my fins", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I got your poker chips. You got my goggles", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yeah I got your fins. You got my poker chips", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "They're next to the fins. You got my cards", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "I guess", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Yeah, see you.", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Are you serious", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Sex... to save the friendship. Well, if we have to...", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "The little extra moan you threw in there. Laying it on a bit thick, don't you think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Mango.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "What am I talking about? Come on. You don't think I bought all that", "qsentId": 62}]